/attach_trailer
Attach the %ls to your truck.

/bonus
Bonus objectives:

/bonus_acceleration
Never release the accelerator while driving

/bonus_birds
Scare 10 birds by using your horn

/bonus_bridge
Don't drive over the bridge

/bonus_cockpit_camera
Always use the cockpit camera when driving

/bonus_cockpit_camera_skidder
Use cockpit camera when delivering the Skidder.

/bonus_cockpit_camera_trailer
Use the cockpit camera when driving with the trailer

/bonus_complete
Bonus objective completed:

/bonus_deliver_uaz
Reach the destination with %ls in the trunk

/bonus_double_uaz
Reach the destination with both %ls trucks

/bonus_extra_points
Find the log trailer, and use it to deliver additional 4 load pts.

/bonus_failed
Bonus objective failed:

/bonus_fences
Don't break any wooden fences

/bonus_flowers
Find fluorescent flowers

/bonus_lane
Don't drive in the opposite road lane

/bonus_night
Complete the challenge during night (until %02d:%02d)

/bonus_night_switch
Complete the challenge at night

/bonus_no_damage
Don't damage your vehicle or any other vehicle

/bonus_no_difflock
Complete the challenge without using the differential lock

/bonus_no_winch
Don't use the winch

/bonus_pumpkin
Find and squash a pumpkin

/bonus_rescue_ural
Tow the %ls out of the water and repair it

/bonus_timer
Deliver the Skidder within %d minutes.

/bonus_timer_left
Time left: %d:%02d

/bonus_trailer_vagon
Reach the destination with the %ls attached

/bonus_watchpoints
Reach every watchpoint

/challenge_fail
You must restart this challenge.

/completed
Completed!

/completion_time_prev
Previous best completion time: %d minutes

/confirm
Start challenge "%ls"?

/crash_desc
Repair and refuel trucks by using other trucks. Then, deliver logs to the %ls.

/crash_fuel_drive
Drive to the %ls to get fuel.
Use the %ls to find the %ls.

/crash_fuel_fuel
Stop the truck and navigate the in-game interface.
Select the %ls option to add fuel to your cistern.

/crash_fuel_fuel_mouse
Stop the truck to see the in-game interface.
Select %ls to add fuel to your cistern.

/crash_fuel_switch
Great! Now switch to the %ls and drive to the %ls to get fuel.

/crash_log_drive
Switch to the %ls and proceed to the %ls to unload.

/crash_nav_switch_hint
You can switch between unlocked trucks using the %ls.

/crash_nav_switch_hint_gamepad
Select %ls and press %ls.

/crash_objective
Unload the %ls at the %ls.

/crash_refuel_drive
Perfect! Now drive back to the %ls to refill it.

/crash_refuel_hint
To refuel the truck, enter the %ls and select the %ls.

/crash_repair
This truck can carry fuel, but it's seriously damaged and needs to be repaired!
Use the %ls to switch to a truck that can perform repairs.

/crash_repair_advanced
Enter the %ls and select %ls.

/crash_repair_drive
Drive the %ls back to the %ls.

/crash_repair_drive_hint
The current vehicle has a %ls add-on that can repair trucks.

/crash_repair_hint
Use the %ls to repair the %ls.

/crash_repair_refuel
Now select %ls and press %ls.

/crash_start
To deliver the logs you're carrying to the %ls, the current truck first needs to be refueled.
Switch to a nearby truck with a fuel tank.

/cruise_accelerate
Now you don't need to hold %ls to accelerate!

/cruise_change
See how the indicator light is lit on the gearstick?
Drag the gearstick to the "1" or "R" gear without deactivating Cruise Control.

/cruise_control
Cruise Control makes the vehicle accelerate so that you don't need to hold %ls while traveling over long distances.

/cruise_hint
Use Cruise Control to accelerate without holding %ls.

/cruise_start
Press and hold %ls to activate Cruise Control.

/cruise_start_mouse
To activate Cruise Control, press %ls or click the tip of the gear stick, then press %ls.

/cruise_success
Perfect! 
To deactivate Cruise Control, press %ls again.
Continue with the challenge.

/deliver_trailer
Detach the %ls at the marked location.

/disabled
Not allowed in this challenge!

/dlc3_01_desc
Find logs in the swamp and bring them to the Lumber Mill.

/dlc3_01_find_logs
Find logs in the swamp and pack them inside your trunk.

/dlc3_01_reach_lumbermill
Reach Lumber Mill and unload.

/dlc3_02_desc
Deliver Skidder loaded onto the flatbed trailer to the target location.

/dlc3_02_go_to_finish
Deliver the trailer with the Skidder to the target location.

/finished
You've completed the challenge!

/gearbox_done
Press %ls again to release the gear stick.

/gearbox_done_action
Release the gear stick.

/gearbox_done_hint
Use %ls to switch to the reverse gear or to go back to automatic gearbox mode if needed.

/gearbox_hint
Use the manual gearbox to crawl!

/gearbox_manual
Use the manual gearbox to limit your vehicle movement speed. This will improve traction and prevent your wheels from digging.

/gearbox_move
Now use the %ls to move the gearstick halfway along gear "1".

/gearbox_move_action
Drag the gear stick.

/gearbox_start
Press %ls to grab and move the gear stick.

/gearbox_start_action
Grab the gear stick.

/gearbox_start_mouse
Press %ls or click the tip of the gear lever.

/gearbox_success
Perfect! 
Now your vehicle will crawl. Note that %ls no longer makes the vehicle reverse, but acts as a brake.
Continue with the challenge.

/hill_desc
Follow the route to get to the top of the hill.

/locked
Complete %ls first

/parking_attach
To attach the trailer, select the trailer attachment socket and press %ls.

/parking_attach_mouse
To attach the trailer, click the trailer attach point.

/parking_attached
Great! Now use the %ls to locate your next destination.

/parking_desc
Pick up a trailer, then drive the rig to a small town.

/parking_detach
Select the %ls option to detach the trailer.

/parking_drive
The navigational route is also visible while driving.
Follow it to find the trailer.

/parking_finish
Drive away from the trailer to complete the challenge.

/parking_nav
Have a look at the navigational route to the %ls, which is marked as a red line.
You can also add, move, or delete navigational route nodes yourself.
Resume the game and follow the route to reach the trailer.

/parking_reverse
Reverse the truck so that the trailer is properly positioned.

/parking_start
The first thing we need to do 
is pick up the trailer. Activate the %ls to locate it.

/parking_trailer_drive
Deliver the trailer to the location marked on the navigational map.

/parking_trailer_nav
Use %ls or %ls to add route nodes and %ls to move the selected node.
Select a node and press %ls to select it.
Hold %ls to remove selected node.

/parking_trailer_nav_mouse
Use the mouse to move and add route nodes.
Double click a node to remove it.

/parking_trailer_positioned
Trailer positioned! Now we need to detach it.
Enter the %ls

/parking_truck_position
Position your truck properly to attach 
the trailer. Reverse towards the trailer.

/parking_truck_positioned
Truck positioned! Now enter the %ls.

/position_truck
Position your vehicle at the marked location.

/primary
Primary objective:

/retry_hint
Completion time: %d minutes.
Play again to clear bonus objectives and improve your completion time.

/river_deep_hint
The water here is too deep. Reverse back immediately and find another way!

/river_desc
Find a route across the wide river with a heavy vehicle.

/river_hint
Proceed slowly. If your vehicle starts to sink, reverse back and find another way.

/river_objective
Drive to the marked location across the river.

/road_desc
Drive a light vehicle through the muddy road.

/sands_desc
Bring a group of two trucks with supplies to the lighthouse along the jagged shoreline.

/sands_objective
Bring %ls, %ls, %ls and %ls to the marked location.

/skidder_fail
The Skidder have fallen off the trailer!

/start
Start challenge

/swamp_attach
Attach the %ls to your truck.

/swamp_cloaking_hint
Reach watchpoints to reveal more of the navigational map!

/swamp_desc
Find the trailer in the swamp and bring it to the camp.

/swamp_find
Find the %ls.

/swamp_tow
Bring the %ls to the marked location.

/switch_to_night
Switch to night

/village_crane
Trigger the %ls to operate the forest crane.

/village_crane_addons
Trigger add-on action %ls.

/village_crane_addons_hint
Before using the forest crane, make sure your truck is positioned correctly.

/village_crane_grab
Press %ls to grab the log and place it inside the trunk.

/village_crane_grab_gamepad
Tilt %ls and %ls to move the crane grabber.

/village_crane_grab_keyboard
Use the keyboard to move the crane grabber.

/village_crane_hint
Use the forest crane to pick up logs and put them in the trunk.

/village_crane_restore
Release the log. Select %ls and hold %ls to restore the crane to its transporting position.

/village_crane_restore_mouse
Release the wooden log and click %ls to restore the crane to its transporting position.

/village_desc
Use the forest crane to collect and pack logs.

/village_drive
Drive to the village.

/village_load_hint
Select a point on the log to see the area where it should be placed.

/village_log_marker
Log

/village_objective
Pack the collected logs together and drive to the marked location.

/village_pack
All logs collected! Now pack them into a stack.

/village_pack_hint
Select any socket point on the logs in the back of the truck and press %ls to pack them.

/village_pack_hint_mouse
Click any point on the wooden logs in the back of the truck to pack them.

/village_position
Position your truck near one of the logs.

/village_position_hint
Don't forget to retract the anchors and proceed to next log location.

/vulkan_desc
Find a way to reach the top of the rocky mountain.

/welcome
Welcome to the challenge!

/winch_drive
You can attach the winch to a truck in front or behind you.
In either case, the other truck can pull or push you to help you move over obstacles.

/winch_drive_attach
Attach the winch from your trailer to the truck behind you.

/winch_drive_attach_engine
Start the engine before using the winch!

/winch_drive_attach_hint
Use the trailer camera mode to view the rear part of the trailer.

/winch_drive_attached
When connected to another truck, a winch can do two things.
%ls. Act as a regular winch.
%ls. Make the other truck accelerate and reverse to follow your truck.
For now, let's switch the winch mode to %ls.

/winch_drive_done
Perfect!
By keeping two trucks connected, they can help each other get past obstacles.
Continue with the challenge.

/winch_drive_hint
Attach the winch to another truck to make it follow you.

/winch_drive_pull
Great! Now press and hold %ls to make the other truck accelerate
and push your truck from behind.

/winch_drive_pull_hint
Press and hold %ls to make the other truck push you.
Note that it may take some time to first start its engine.

/winch_drive_reverse
If your truck is reversing, press and hold %ls to make the other truck reverse, too, pulling you along.
Press %ls to switch to reverse gear. You can also use the manual gearbox.

/winch_drive_reverse_pull
Press and hold %ls to make the other truck reverse.

/winch_drive_switch
Enter the %ls and select [%ls%ls]
