/awd_fuel
The truck consumes more fuel with %ls engaged.

/camera
First of all, let's have a look around.

/camera_hint
Tilt %ls to move the camera.

/camera_hint_mouse
Click the left mouse button, then move the mouse to move the camera.
Click the left mouse button again to stop moving the camera.

/camera_legacy
That was legacy MUDRUNNER™ camera controls. 
We will now switch the game to use %ls mode. 
You can change that in %ls menu.

/disabled
Not available in the tutorial!

/dl_wheels
%ls makes all vehicle wheels spin evenly, but makes it harder to control.

/drive
Ok, now let's drive!

/drive_hint
Release the parking brake and drive along the asphalt road.

/fail
You must restart the tutorial.
Drive safely!

/finished
You've finished the tutorial!

/garage
You've arrived at the %ls, where you can install add-ons and trailers. 
Your truck can also be rescued and brought back to the garage if you're playing in %ls Mode.

/install
Select the 
%ls option, then select %ls, and press %ls.

/install_addon
For the purpose of this tutorial, please install %ls.

/install_done
Great!
Now drive to the %ls.

/install_mouse
Double click %ls below %ls to install the add-on.

/lumber
Here you can load up your truck.
Different log types have different amounts of load points.
Our current truck can only be loaded with %ls.

/lumber_done
Good! 
Now let's proceed to our final destination, the %ls.

/lumber_drive
Release the parking brake and drive to the %ls.

/lumber_hint
To load up your truck, select the icon with the %ls and hold %ls.

/lumber_hint_mouse
To load up your truck, double click the icon with %ls.

/mud
You've approached a muddy road.

/mud_drive
Drive along the muddy road with 
%ls and %ls engaged.

/mud_hint
Engage All Wheel Drive and Differential Lock.

/objective
Perfect!
It's now time to unload your truck. But remember, this would only be 
2 out of 8 Load Points total required to fill up the %ls in a real game.

/objective_done
This tutorial didn't cover everything in the game.
Try a %ls to learn more!

/objective_drive
Release the parking brake and proceed along the road.

/objective_hint
Select %ls and press %ls to complete the tutorial.

/pregarage_hint
Proceed along the road towards the buildings.

/prewinch_hint
Release the parking brake and keep driving along the road.

/switch
Now let's switch to this truck. 
To do so, enter %ls and select the %ls option.

/switch_done
Good work! 
Note that this truck is rear drive only and doesn't have differential lock.

/switch_hint
Select the %ls option.

/switch_hint_advanced
Move the camera so you can see the %ls, select it, and press %ls.

/switch_hint_advanced_mouse
Move the camera so you can see the %ls, then click it.

/title
Welcome to MUDRUNNER!

/truck
You're now approaching another truck.
In MUDRUNNER™, you can switch between trucks that you've unlocked.

/truck_hint
Drive closer to the truck.

/unlock
To access the garage, you must first unlock access to it by delivering 4 garage points.
Someone has already delivered 3 points to this garage. Because your truck has 1 point, we can now unlock it.

/unlock_done
Done! Your truck gets fully repaired when you visit an unlocked garage, but gets refueled for only up to %d liters.
The aim of the game is to deliver logs to the %ls, so now let's install an add-on that carries logs.

/unlock_hint
Select %ls and press %ls.

/welcome
This tutorial will show you basic game concepts.

/winch_attach
Move the camera until you find a suitable winch point and press %ls.

/winch_done
Very good!
Release the winch and proceed along the road toward the buildings.

/winch_drive
Pull the winch and accelerate at the same time to move further along the road.

/winch_hint
Proceed along the road using the winch to help climb up the hill.

/winch_hint_mouse
Left click a point on your truck, then click a point on a tree to attach the winch.

/winch_release
To detach the winch, select %ls 
and use the %ls option.

/winch_release_advanced
To detach the winch, use the %ls function.

/winch_release_mouse
To detach the winch, click the cross icon
at the end of the winch rope, or activate %ls
and use the %ls function.

/winch_socket_mouse
Select winch point

/winch_stage
Each truck in MUDRUNNER™ is equipped with a winch 
that you can attach to nearby trees or vehicles.

/winch_stage_gamepad
Let's use Quick Winch Mode to pull ourselves over the hill.

/winch_stage_mouse
Let's use it to pull ourselves over the hill.

/winch_start
Press %ls to enter Quick Winch Mode.
